Hello hello hello friends
welcome to Pooja Computer once again I
will tell you everything in today's topic friends
you can do personal accident from CSC digital seva portal
see
how will you do personal accident insurance from HDFC Agro General
Insurance see we have
logged in to CSC digital seva portal but
after logging in you have to
click on this red button after clicking on the insurance button
see it will come at the bottom
then personal accident an option is given
after clicking on it see
here personal accident HDFC
ergo general insurance click here button after that click on
CSC connect button after that
click on health button
see in the previous video it was told to do
hospital Delhi gas insurance okay
in today's video we will tell you ma tel the
medicine vote super here see Arogya
Sanjivani for Arogya Sanjivani insurance
in this video we will tell you
what is Arogya Sanjivani what does it cover up to
how many days is it insured, we
will tell you all this in this video and it is
very good friends and it covers everything
it means children  Insurance covers everything from this, if there is an
accident like this, it is a
disease, similarly if you have
any problem then your entire expense is
provided to you, so see how to
do this
remedy, click on the subscribe button,
after clicking see, it is asking like this,
here it is asking if
you want to do it for Candy Crush game, then
write here
your friend, write this and if you
want to do it for children also, then it is
written fine, otherwise
click on Direct Individual here, but you
can also add children, the number of
children you have and one of four cloves will write, if there is
control then their electricity or if you
want to do it for your wife also, then
write for wife here, this page will type,
after that also you will click on the vote button,
after that it will ask for your name here or it has happened
that A
and after that you have to enter the mobile number here,
after that you have to click on the retirement mark button,
also you have to click on the Dhulkot button,
see your plan has come like this, it is
written that this is a plan of three lakhs, you will get
this on premium  You have to pay Rs 4613, if you take three and a half
lakhs then you will have to pay at 4712, if you
take four lakhs then your 48 will fall on 12
and if you take four plugs for 50,000 then you will have to
stop at 49 times and make your face,
then comment Sapna, complete details here, by
clicking on Bhim and you can see what all will be
covered in it, your
total details are given here, it is
suitable for Indian cricket, on that you will get
hospitalization, students will get payment,
subscription, colleges, hospitals, Jatin's
yoga will be appointed,
you will get the best treatment, and
see here you will have to pay ₹40 as premium plus GST 18 per
cent for pizza, total of yours is
500 to 1000, after that
if you want to do it simply then
click on the Simply Profit button, now let's see
what all details it is asking for,
here it is asking for your date of birth,
see here it is asking for your pin code,
enter the pin code, it is done, it is done
[Music]
after entering the pin code here
I have taken a pin code here,
see the state is coming, Sadhna city has come, there is a
length mark, then you can give something,
after that click on the proceed button,
see here it is asking for height, enter it,
or
here health care, do you need any health complaint,
accident history, hospital
reaction history and surgery, if
you already have something here then you can say yes,
if not then click on servant,
or after that click on the button,
after that see here it is asking for the name of the nominee, do you
want to make this, type their name,
type their relation here, or
here in Airtel the conditioner is asking did
you have any existing HDFC Hair Co hair serum,
if yes then say yes, otherwise
click here and
click on the family profit button,
after that see the director's name will appear here,
see you have got 50% rural sector
discount, see in this you have got a discount of 15 percent off,
if  If you are
from rural area then the initial premium was to be fixed at
₹40 but in the new premium you will have to pay ₹
40, simply
click on the famous button after seeing the terms and
conditions, simply click on the statement condition button
and click on the buy name,
see here your transaction
number has come here, simply
click on it and a
photo
of it will directly take you to the payment options here
and simply
after making your payment your
payment will be done directly and you will be insured
with HDFC Agro, so in this way friends
you can get insurance for personal
accident and by doing so you can make cigarettes worth your while,
how did you like this video friends if you liked the
video then like, subscribe and
share, that's all in today's video, we will meet
with the next topic till then
bye Jai Hind Jai Bharat